<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FlowerObjectDetection</string>
    <string name="lOgin">Login</string>
    <string name="petal">Firebase Auth</string>


    <string name="eggplant">
- Eggplant (Solanum melongena), also known as aubergine or brinjal in different regions.\n

Origin:
- Likely originated in Southeast Asia or India.
\n- Cultivated since ancient times, with spread to the Middle East and Europe over centuries.

\nPurpose:
- Primarily used as a vegetable in cooking.\n
- Known for its versatility in culinary uses, including grilling, frying, baking, and as an ingredient in stews and dips.

\nBenefits:
- Rich in fiber, antioxidants, and vitamins such as vitamin C, vitamin K, and B vitamins.\n
- Contains manganese and other minerals essential for bone health.\n
- Low in calories, making it beneficial for weight management.\n
- May help support heart health, lower cholesterol, and improve blood sugar control.

\nFamily:
- Belongs to the Solanaceae family, which includes tomatoes, potatoes, and peppers.

\nFamous Varieties:
- Popular varieties include Black Beauty, Italian, Japanese, and Chinese eggplants.\n
- Known for various shapes and colors, from deep purple to white and even green.

\nClimate and Season:
- Thrives in warm, tropical to subtropical climates.\n
- Sensitive to cold; best grown in temperatures between 70°F and 85°F (21°C - 29°C).

\nHow to Plant:
- Start seeds indoors 8-10 weeks before the last expected frost.\n
- Transplant young plants outside when temperatures are consistently warm and frost risk has passed.\n
- Ensure soil is well-draining, fertile, and enriched with compost or manure.

\nHow to Manage:
- Requires consistent watering, especially during flowering and fruiting stages.\n
- Mulch around plants to retain moisture and prevent weeds.\n
- Stake plants if they grow tall and need support.\n
- Watch for pests like aphids, flea beetles, and spider mites, and treat as needed.

\nMonths to Harvest:
- Typically ready for harvest 70-85 days after transplanting.\n
- Ideal time to harvest is when fruits are glossy and firm but before seeds become large and tough.\n

\nConclusion:
\n Eggplants are a versatile and nutritious vegetable that has been cherished across cultures for centuries. With a range of health benefits, from fiber and antioxidants to essential vitamins, they are an excellent addition to a balanced diet. While they thrive in warm weather,eggplants require careful planting, watering, and pest management to produce optimal yields. With patience and attention to their growing needs, eggplants can be a rewarding crop, yielding delicious and nutritious fruits that add flavor and depth to countless dishes."

    </string>
    <string name="sunflowerinfo">
- Sunflower (Helianthus annuus), commonly known as the sunflower, is a vibrant flowering plant admired for its large, sun-like blooms and versatile uses, ranging from ornamental decoration to food and oil production.

\nOrigin:
- Native to North America, specifically the central and western regions of the United States.\n
- Cultivated by indigenous peoples over 4,500 years ago for food, oil, and dye.

\nPurpose:
- Primarily grown for its seeds, which are a source of oil and snack food.\n
- Used ornamentally for its striking yellow flowers that symbolize warmth and positivity.\n
- Plays a role in phytoremediation, helping to extract toxins from the soil, including heavy metals.\n
- Provides food and habitat for pollinators like bees and birds.

\nBenefits:
- Nutritional Value: Seeds are rich in healthy fats, protein, vitamin E, magnesium, and selenium.\n
- Oil Uses: Sunflower oil is used in cooking and cosmetics for its light texture and high vitamin E content.\n
- Environmental Role: Acts as a natural barrier against wind erosion and supports biodiversity.\n
- Cultural Symbolism: Represents adoration, loyalty, and longevity in various cultures.

\nFamily:
- Belongs to the Asteraceae family, commonly known as the daisy or composite family.

\nFamous Varieties:
- Helianthus annuus (common sunflower) – the most widely cultivated species.\n
- Mammoth Sunflower – known for its large heads and edible seeds.\n
- Teddy Bear Sunflower – a dwarf variety with fluffy, double blooms.\n
- Autumn Beauty – features orange, red, and yellow multi-colored flowers.

\nClimate and Season:
- Thrives in temperate climates with plenty of sunlight.\n
- Requires full sun for at least 6–8 hours daily.\n
- Best grown in temperatures between 70°F and 78°F (21°C - 26°C).

\nHow to Plant:
- Plant seeds directly in the soil after the last frost when temperatures are consistently warm.\n
- Use well-drained, nutrient-rich soil with a neutral to slightly acidic pH (6.0–7.5).\n
- Space seeds 6–12 inches apart, depending on the variety, and plant them about 1 inch deep.\n
- Water regularly during germination, ensuring soil stays moist but not soggy.

\nHow to Manage:
- Water deeply but infrequently to encourage deep root growth.\n
- Fertilize with a balanced fertilizer or compost during the growing season.\n
- Stake tall varieties to prevent them from toppling in strong winds.\n
- Protect from pests like aphids, caterpillars, and birds by using nets or natural deterrents.

\nMonths to Bloom:
- Typically blooms in summer and early fall, about 80–120 days after planting, depending on the variety.\n
- Flowers last for several weeks and turn towards the sun during their growth phase (a behavior called heliotropism).

\nConclusion:
\n Sunflowers are more than just a beautiful addition to gardens; they offer nutritional, ecological, and symbolic value. With their ability to adapt to various climates, provide essential resources, and enhance soil health, sunflowers are a versatile and sustainable plant. Their vibrant blooms and diverse uses make them a favorite among gardeners, farmers, and nature enthusiasts alike.

    </string>
    <string name="bougainvilleainfo">
- Bougainvillea (Bougainvillea spp.), often referred to as "paper flower" due to its thin, colorful bracts resembling paper, is a tropical and subtropical plant widely admired for its vibrant appearance.

\nOrigin:
- Native to South America, specifically Brazil, Peru, and Argentina.\n
- Named after Louis Antoine de Bougainville, a French admiral and explorer.

\nPurpose:
- Primarily used as an ornamental plant due to its vibrant, colorful bracts.\n
- Commonly grown in gardens, fences, arbors, and as potted plants for decoration.\n
- Sometimes used for erosion control on slopes and hillsides.

\nBenefits:
- Provides shade and privacy as a natural barrier or hedge.\n
- Enhances air quality by absorbing carbon dioxide and releasing oxygen.\n
- Acts as a habitat for birds, butterflies, and beneficial insects.\n
- Certain parts, such as flowers, are used in traditional medicine to treat coughs and regulate blood sugar levels.

\nFamily:
- Belongs to the Nyctaginaceae family, commonly called the four o’clock family.

\nFamous Varieties:
- Bougainvillea glabra (less thorny, compact bracts, often purple).\n
- Bougainvillea spectabilis (larger flowers and leaves, more vigorous).\n
- Hybrid varieties like "Barbara Karst" (bright red) and "Afterglow" (orange).

\nClimate and Season:
- Thrives in tropical and subtropical climates.\n
- Requires full sun for at least 6 hours daily to bloom well.\n
- Drought-tolerant but prefers warm weather, with an ideal temperature range of 70°F to 95°F (21°C - 35°C).

\nHow to Plant:
- Plant in well-draining, slightly acidic soil (pH 5.5 to 6.0).\n
- Choose a sunny location with space for its growth.\n
- Use cuttings or rooted plants for faster establishment.

\nHow to Manage:
- Water sparingly; overwatering can lead to root rot and reduced blooming.\n
- Prune regularly to control shape, encourage growth, and promote flowering.\n
- Use a low-nitrogen, high-phosphorus fertilizer to boost blooms.\n
- Protect from frost or cold drafts during winter months.

\nMonths to Bloom:
- Blooms throughout the year in tropical regions.\n
- In temperate areas, blooms primarily from spring to autumn.\n
- Flowers last longer in dry seasons due to less water stress.

\nConclusion:
\n Bougainvillea is a stunning, low-maintenance plant that thrives in warm climates and adds beauty to gardens with its vibrant bracts and lush foliage. Ideal for decorative purposes, it also supports local ecosystems by attracting pollinators. With proper care, including sunlight, minimal watering, and occasional pruning, bougainvillea can flourish and bring life to any outdoor or indoor space.

    </string>
    <string name="climbingroseinfo">
- Climbing Rose (Rosa spp.), often simply called climbing rose, is a type of rose plant known for its ability to grow vertically along trellises, walls, and arbors, producing clusters of fragrant and colorful blooms.

\nOrigin:
- Climbing roses are derived from various wild rose species, primarily native to Europe, North America, and Asia.\n
- Cultivated for centuries for ornamental purposes and crossbred to produce a variety of colors and forms.

\nPurpose:
- Grown primarily as ornamental plants for vertical gardening on trellises, fences, arbors, and walls.\n
- Enhances garden aesthetics with its romantic, cascading blooms.\n
- Provides habitat and food for pollinators like bees and butterflies.

\nBenefits:
- Visual Appeal: Adds height, dimension, and vibrant color to gardens.\n
- Fragrance: Many varieties emit a strong, pleasant aroma that enhances outdoor spaces.\n
- Pollinator Attraction: Supports local ecosystems by drawing beneficial insects.\n
- Erosion Control: When planted on slopes, climbing roses help reduce soil erosion.

\nFamily:
- Belongs to the Rosaceae family, which includes other plants like apples, cherries, and strawberries.

\nFamous Varieties:
- Iceberg Climbing Rose: White blooms with a mild fragrance.\n
- Don Juan: Deep red, velvety flowers with a strong scent.\n
- New Dawn: Pale pink blooms, hardy and disease-resistant.\n
- Golden Showers: Bright yellow flowers with a light, sweet scent.

\nClimate and Season:
- Thrives in temperate climates with full sun exposure for at least 6–8 hours daily.\n
- Best grown in regions with well-defined seasons, though some varieties tolerate warmer climates.\n
- Typically blooms in late spring to early summer, with repeat blooms in some varieties.

\nHow to Plant:
- Choose a location with good air circulation and at least 6 hours of direct sunlight daily.\n
- Prepare well-drained, nutrient-rich soil with a slightly acidic to neutral pH (6.0–7.0).\n
- Plant bare-root roses in early spring, spacing them 3–5 feet apart.\n
- Dig a hole twice as wide as the root ball, mix compost into the soil, and water thoroughly after planting.

\nHow to Manage:
- Provide sturdy support, such as a trellis, arbor, or wall, for the roses to climb.\n
- Prune annually to shape the plant, remove deadwood, and encourage healthy growth.\n
- Fertilize in spring and summer with rose-specific or balanced fertilizers.\n
- Water deeply but infrequently, avoiding wetting the leaves to prevent fungal diseases.\n
- Watch for pests like aphids, spider mites, and black spot, and treat as necessary with organic or chemical solutions.

\nMonths to Bloom:
- Blooming begins in late spring and continues through summer, with some varieties blooming again in autumn.\n
- Repeat-blooming varieties produce flowers multiple times during the growing season.

\nConclusion:
\n Climbing roses are a stunning addition to any garden, offering height, beauty, and fragrance. Their versatility allows them to be trained along structures, making them perfect for vertical gardens and privacy screens. With proper care, including pruning, fertilizing, and pest management, climbing roses reward gardeners with vibrant, long-lasting blooms that transform any outdoor space into a romantic retreat.

    </string>
    <string name="aloeverainfo">
- Aloe vera (Aloe barbadensis miller), often known simply as aloe, is a succulent plant species recognized for its thick, fleshy leaves that store water and its medicinal properties.

\nOrigin:
- Aloe vera is native to the Arabian Peninsula but is now widely cultivated in tropical and subtropical regions around the world.\n
- It has been used for centuries for its healing properties, particularly in skin care and traditional medicine.

\nPurpose:
- Grown primarily for its medicinal and cosmetic uses, especially for treating burns, wounds, and skin irritation.\n
- Used as a natural remedy for digestive issues in some cultures.\n
- Popular in the production of health supplements, lotions, and gels.

\nBenefits:
- Skin Care: Aloe vera gel is known for its soothing and moisturizing properties, often used to treat sunburns, cuts, and skin irritation.\n
- Healing Properties: Helps in the healing of minor burns, cuts, and wounds due to its anti-inflammatory and antimicrobial properties.\n
- Digestive Health: When consumed, aloe vera juice can promote digestion and soothe the gastrointestinal tract.\n
- Air Purification: Aloe vera is considered an air-purifying plant that helps remove toxins from the indoor environment.

\nFamily:
- Belongs to the Asphodelaceae family, which includes other plants like haworthia and gasteria.

\nFamous Varieties:
- Aloe Vera Barbadensis Miller: The most commonly used variety for medicinal and cosmetic purposes.\n
- Aloe Vera Chinensis: Known for its thinner leaves and high gel content.\n
- Aloe Vera Saponaria: Commonly used in tropical areas for its medicinal properties.

\nClimate and Season:
- Thrives in warm, sunny climates with well-drained, sandy or loamy soil.\n
- Best grown in areas with mild winters and hot summers.\n
- Aloe vera can bloom year-round in ideal conditions but typically flowers in the spring.

\nHow to Plant:
- Choose a location with plenty of direct sunlight (at least 6 hours per day).\n
- Use well-draining soil, preferably a cactus or succulent mix.\n
- Plant in a pot with drainage holes if growing indoors.\n
- Water sparingly, letting the soil dry completely between waterings, and avoid overwatering.

\nHow to Manage:
- Aloe vera is a low-maintenance plant, needing minimal care once established.\n
- Ensure it receives plenty of sunlight and water only when the soil is dry to the touch.\n
- Remove any dead or damaged leaves to keep the plant healthy.\n
- Repot every 2-3 years to prevent root crowding, especially if growing in a container.

\nMonths to Bloom:
- Aloe vera typically blooms in the spring or summer, producing tall flower spikes with tubular yellow or orange flowers.\n
- Not all aloe vera plants will bloom, especially those grown in containers or indoor environments.

\nConclusion:
\n Aloe vera is a versatile and hardy plant, prized for its many health benefits and minimal care requirements. Ideal for both indoor and outdoor gardening, it’s a valuable addition to any home, offering medicinal and cosmetic uses while enhancing the beauty of your garden or living space. With proper care, aloe vera can thrive for years, providing soothing relief for skin and digestive issues.

    </string>
    <string name="cosmosinfo">
- Cosmos (Cosmos spp.) is a genus of flowering plants in the Asteraceae family, known for their bright, daisy-like flowers and graceful appearance. They are commonly grown in gardens for their vibrant blooms and ease of cultivation.

\nOrigin:
- Cosmos is native to Mexico, though it is now widely grown in temperate and tropical regions around the world.\n
- It has been cultivated since the 18th century, mainly for ornamental purposes.

\nPurpose:
- Primarily grown as ornamental plants in gardens and landscapes.\n
- Attracts pollinators like bees, butterflies, and birds, making it beneficial for biodiversity.\n
- Used in flower arrangements and as cut flowers due to their long-lasting blooms.

\nBenefits:
- Visual Appeal: Cosmos flowers come in vibrant colors such as pink, red, white, and purple, adding beauty and brightness to any garden.
- Pollinator Attraction: The flowers attract pollinators, supporting local ecosystems and promoting the health of other plants.
- Low Maintenance: Cosmos are drought-tolerant and require minimal care, making them ideal for beginner gardeners.
- Edible Seeds: Some species of cosmos produce edible seeds that can be used in cooking, though this is less common.

\nFamily:
- Belongs to the Asteraceae family, which includes other plants like sunflowers, daisies, and asters.

\nFamous Varieties:
- Cosmos bipinnatus (Garden Cosmos): The most common variety with large, showy flowers in shades of pink, red, and white.\n
- Cosmos sulphureus (Yellow Cosmos): Known for its bright yellow or orange flowers.\n
- Cosmos atrosanguineus (Chocolate Cosmos): Famous for its deep red to almost black flowers and a scent that resembles chocolate.

\nClimate and Season:
- Thrives in full sun and well-drained soil.\n
- Prefers warm climates but can grow in a variety of conditions, making it suitable for temperate and tropical areas.\n
- Blooms from summer to fall, with some varieties continuing until the first frost.

\nHow to Plant:
- Choose a sunny location with well-drained soil, as Cosmos do not tolerate wet roots.\n
- Cosmos grow best when direct-sown into the ground after the last frost, but can also be started indoors and transplanted.\n
- Space seeds or seedlings about 12–18 inches apart, as they can grow tall and need room to spread.\n
- Water gently, allowing the soil to dry between waterings to prevent root rot.

\nHow to Manage:
- Cosmos are very low-maintenance, needing only occasional watering and a light feeding with a balanced fertilizer.\n
- Deadheading (removing spent flowers) can encourage continuous blooming throughout the growing season.\n
- Tall varieties may require staking or support to keep the flowers upright, especially in windy areas.\n
- Watch for pests like aphids and caterpillars, and treat as necessary with organic solutions.

\nMonths to Bloom:
- Cosmos typically begin blooming in mid to late summer, continuing through to the first frost.\n
- Some varieties bloom more profusely if deadheaded regularly, ensuring a long-lasting display.

\nConclusion:
\n Cosmos are beautiful, hardy plants that add color and charm to any garden. With their attractive flowers and ability to thrive in a variety of conditions, they are an excellent choice for gardeners looking for an easy-care, visually appealing plant. Whether grown in garden beds, borders, or containers, cosmos plants are a delightful addition that supports pollinator populations and provides long-lasting blooms throughout the growing season.

    </string>
    <string name="forgetmenotinfo">
- Forget-Me-Not (Myosotis spp.) is a small, perennial flowering plant known for its delicate blue flowers with yellow centers, though they can also come in shades of pink and white. They are commonly grown for their charming appearance and are often used in gardens and as symbols of remembrance.

\nOrigin:
- Forget-me-nots are native to Europe and Asia, though they have been widely cultivated in gardens around the world.\n
- They have a long history of use in ornamental gardening and symbolism, particularly in memorial or remembrance contexts.

\nPurpose:
- Primarily grown as ornamental plants in gardens, providing a soft, colorful ground cover or accent in borders.\n
- Often associated with memory and remembrance, especially in the language of flowers, where they symbolize true love and remembrance.\n
- Attracts pollinators like bees and butterflies, contributing to local ecosystems.

\nBenefits:
- Visual Appeal: The bright blue flowers add a touch of softness and charm to gardens, particularly in spring and early summer.\n
- Pollinator Attraction: The flowers are excellent for attracting bees and butterflies, promoting pollination in the garden.\n
- Symbolism: Often used in memorial gardens or as a symbol of remembrance, loyalty, and love.\n
- Ground Cover: Suitable for use as ground cover or edging plants due to their spreading growth habit.

\nFamily:
- Belongs to the Boraginaceae family, which includes other plants like borage and lungwort.

\nFamous Varieties:
- Myosotis sylvatica (Wood Forget-Me-Not): The most common variety, with vibrant blue flowers and a compact growth habit.\n
- Myosotis alpestris (Alpine Forget-Me-Not): A variety native to high-altitude regions, known for its smaller, intense blue flowers.\n
- Myosotis discolor (Changing Forget-Me-Not): Features pale blue to pink flowers that change color as they mature.

\nClimate and Season:
- Prefers cool to temperate climates and partial to full shade.\n
- Grows best in regions with mild temperatures and moderate moisture.\n
- Typically blooms in spring to early summer, though some varieties may bloom sporadically through the year.

\nHow to Plant:
- Choose a location with well-drained, humus-rich soil, preferably in partial to full shade, though some varieties tolerate sun.\n
- Forget-me-nots can be started from seeds, which should be sown directly in the soil in early spring or fall.\n
- Space the plants about 6–12 inches apart to allow for spreading growth.\n
- Water regularly, ensuring the soil stays moist but not waterlogged.

\nHow to Manage:
- Keep the soil moist but not soggy, as forget-me-nots do not tolerate dry conditions.\n
- Deadhead spent flowers to encourage additional blooms and prevent the plant from becoming too leggy.\n
- Divide plants every few years to prevent overcrowding and to encourage healthy growth.\n
- May need protection from hot, dry summers, particularly in areas with intense sun.

\nMonths to Bloom:
- Forget-me-nots typically bloom from early spring to early summer, with some varieties producing flowers until mid-summer.\n
- Blooms last for several weeks, and deadheading can extend the blooming period.

\nConclusion:
\n Forget-me-nots are charming, low-maintenance plants that add a touch of delicate beauty to any garden. With their bright blue flowers and symbolic meanings, they are perfect for adding color to shaded areas, rock gardens, or as part of a memorial garden. Easy to grow and care for, forget-me-nots are a lovely addition to any landscape, supporting pollinators while also holding sentimental value for gardeners.

    </string>
    <string name="frangipaniinfo">
- Frangipani (Plumeria), is a tropical and subtropical flowering plant known for its large, fragrant blooms that come in shades of white, pink, red, yellow, and multicolored varieties. These flowers are widely loved for their beauty and heavenly scent, often associated with tropical gardens and leis.

\nOrigin:
- Native to the Americas, specifically Mexico, Central America, and the Caribbean.\n
- Widely cultivated across tropical and subtropical regions worldwide, including Southeast Asia and the Pacific Islands.

\nPurpose:
- Ornamental Use: Popular in gardens, courtyards, and as street trees for their vibrant flowers and soothing fragrance.\n
- Cultural Significance: Used in traditional ceremonies, garlands (leis), and religious rituals in many cultures.\n
- Perfume Industry: The fragrance of frangipani is often used in perfumes and skincare products.

\nBenefits:
- Visual Appeal: The vibrant, showy flowers enhance the aesthetic of gardens and landscapes.\n
- Fragrance: Renowned for its sweet, intoxicating scent, especially noticeable at night.\n
- Attracts Pollinators: Lures moths and butterflies, contributing to biodiversity in gardens.\n
- Medicinal Uses: In traditional medicine, various parts of the plant are used for treating ailments like inflammation, fever, and skin issues.\n
- Drought Tolerance: Thrives in dry conditions, making it ideal for water-scarce regions.

\nFamily:
- Belongs to the Apocynaceae family, which also includes plants like oleander and periwinkle.

\nFamous Varieties:
- Plumeria rubra: Known for its vibrant red, pink, and white flowers.
- Plumeria obtusa (Singapore Graveyard Flower): Features white flowers with a yellow center and glossy, dark green leaves.
- Plumeria alba: Produces fragrant white flowers with a yellow core, often grown in warm climates.

\nClimate and Season:
- Thrives in warm, tropical to subtropical climates.
- Prefers full sun but can tolerate partial shade.
- Blooms in late spring through early fall, with peak flowering in summer.

\nHow to Plant:
- Location: Choose a sunny spot with well-draining soil.
- Propagation: Easily propagated from cuttings. Allow cuttings to dry for a few days before planting to prevent rotting.
- Planting Depth: Plant cuttings or saplings in soil, keeping the roots shallow and watering sparingly at first.
- Spacing: Ensure ample space (6–12 feet apart) for mature trees to spread.

\nHow to Manage:
- Watering: Water deeply but infrequently; allow the soil to dry out between waterings.
- Pruning: Remove dead or diseased branches to maintain shape and encourage new growth.
- Fertilizing: Use a low-nitrogen, high-phosphorus fertilizer during the growing season for abundant blooms.
- Pest Control: Watch for pests like spider mites or whiteflies; treat with insecticidal soap if necessary.

\nMonths to Bloom:
- Frangipani typically blooms from late spring to early fall, depending on the climate. In warm regions, flowering may extend through the year.

\nConclusion:
\n Frangipani is a stunning, fragrant addition to any garden, beloved for its vibrant, long-lasting blooms and cultural significance. Its easy care, drought tolerance, and ability to attract pollinators make it a versatile plant suitable for tropical and subtropical landscapes. Whether planted as a centerpiece in a garden or lining a pathway, frangipani brings beauty and serenity to any space.

    </string>
    <string name="gumamelainfo">
- Gumamela (Hibiscus rosa-sinensis), also known as Hibiscus, is a tropical flowering plant recognized for its large, colorful blooms in shades of red, pink, yellow, orange, and white. The flowers are trumpet-shaped with prominent stamens, making them a striking feature in gardens and landscapes.

\nOrigin:
- Native to Asia, particularly in regions such as India, China, and the Philippines.
- Widely cultivated in tropical and subtropical areas across the globe.

\nPurpose:
- Ornamental Use: Popular for beautifying gardens, parks, and patios due to its vivid and showy flowers.
- Cultural Significance: Used in traditional ceremonies and decorations in many Southeast Asian cultures.
- Medicinal Applications: Utilized in folk medicine to treat ailments such as cough, fever, and skin conditions.

\nBenefits:
- Aesthetic Appeal: Adds a splash of vibrant color to gardens and landscapes.
- Medicinal Properties: Flowers and leaves are used for remedies like herbal teas, poultices, and treatments for respiratory issues.
- Eco-friendly: Attracts pollinators such as bees, butterflies, and hummingbirds, fostering biodiversity.
- Ease of Growth: Thrives in various soil types and climates, making it a low-maintenance choice for gardeners.

\nFamily:
- Belongs to the Malvaceae family, which includes other plants like cotton and okra.

\nFamous Varieties:
- Hibiscus rosa-sinensis (Chinese Hibiscus): Known for its large, brightly colored flowers.
- Hibiscus syriacus (Rose of Sharon): Produces small, delicate blooms in pink, lavender, or white.
- Hibiscus sabdariffa (Roselle): Valued for its edible calyces, often used in teas and jams.

\nClimate and Season:
- Prefers warm, humid climates but can adapt to subtropical regions.
- Thrives in full sun but tolerates partial shade.
- Blooms year-round in tropical climates, with peak flowering during warmer months.

\nHow to Plant:
- Location: Choose a sunny spot with well-draining soil.
- Propagation: Propagate through stem cuttings or seeds. Cuttings root easily when planted in moist soil.
- Planting Depth: Plant cuttings or saplings with roots just below the soil surface.
- Spacing: Space plants about 3–6 feet apart to allow for proper air circulation.

\nHow to Manage:
- Watering: Keep the soil consistently moist but avoid waterlogging.
- Pruning: Regularly trim to remove dead flowers and branches, encouraging healthy growth and new blooms.
- Fertilizing: Use a balanced fertilizer during the growing season for optimal flowering.
- Pest Control: Watch for aphids, spider mites, and whiteflies; use neem oil or insecticidal soap as needed.

\nMonths to Bloom:
- Gumamela flowers year-round in tropical climates. In cooler regions, blooming is prominent during late spring and summer.

\nConclusion:
\n The Gumamela is a vibrant and versatile plant that brings life and color to any garden. Its low-maintenance nature, medicinal properties, and ecological benefits make it a valuable addition to both private and public landscapes. Whether grown as a hedge, potted plant, or garden centerpiece, the Gumamela captivates with its enduring beauty and charm.

    </string>
    <string name="zinniainfo">
- Zinnias (Zinnia elegans) are cheerful, vibrant flowering plants known for their daisy-like or dome-shaped blooms in a wide variety of colors, including red, orange, yellow, pink, purple, white, and even multi-colored patterns. Beloved for their long-lasting blooms, zinnias are a favorite among gardeners for adding a splash of color to gardens and landscapes.

\nOrigin:
- Native to Mexico and Central America.
- Cultivated worldwide in gardens for their bright, striking flowers.

\nPurpose:
- Ornamental Use: Commonly grown in flower beds, borders, and containers for their colorful blooms.
- Cut Flowers: Popular in floral arrangements and bouquets due to their long vase life.
- Attracting Pollinators: Their bright colors and nectar attract butterflies, bees, and hummingbirds.

\nBenefits:
- Aesthetic Value: Enhances the visual appeal of gardens and landscapes.
- Low Maintenance: Easy to grow, making them ideal for beginners.
- Biodiversity Support: Attracts beneficial pollinators to the garden.
- Heat Tolerance: Thrives in hot, sunny conditions, requiring minimal care.

\nFamily:
- Belongs to the Asteraceae family, which also includes sunflowers, daisies, and marigolds.

\nFamous Varieties:
- Zinnia elegans (Common Zinnia): Known for its wide range of colors and forms.
- Zinnia angustifolia (Creeping Zinnia): Features smaller, daisy-like flowers, perfect for ground cover.
- Zinnia haageana (Mexican Zinnia): Compact plants with small, bicolored blooms.
- Dreamland Series: Dwarf plants with large, fully double flowers.

\nClimate and Season:
- Thrives in warm climates with full sun exposure.
- Prefers well-drained soil and tolerates drought once established.
- Blooms from late spring through fall, with peak flowering in summer.

\nHow to Plant:
- Location: Choose a sunny area with good air circulation and well-draining soil.
- Propagation: Grown from seeds sown directly into the soil or started indoors.
- Planting Depth: Sow seeds about 1/4 inch deep and cover lightly with soil.
- Spacing: Space plants 6–18 inches apart, depending on the variety.

\nHow to Manage:
- Watering: Water deeply but infrequently, allowing the soil to dry out between watering to prevent root rot.
- Deadheading: Regularly remove spent blooms to encourage continuous flowering.
- Fertilizing: Apply a balanced fertilizer every 4–6 weeks during the growing season.
- Pest Control: Monitor for aphids, spider mites, and powdery mildew; treat with insecticidal soap or neem oil as necessary.

\nMonths to Bloom:
- Zinnias bloom from late spring to the first frost, providing a long season of vibrant flowers.

\nConclusion:
\n Zinnias are a delightful addition to any garden, offering easy care, vivid colors, and the ability to attract pollinators. Their versatility makes them ideal for borders, containers, or cut flower arrangements. Whether grown by experienced gardeners or beginners, zinnias provide lasting beauty and joy throughout the growing season.

    </string>

    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password" />
    <string name="logo_description" />
    <string name="register" />
    <string name="click_to_login">Click to login</string>
    <string name="click_to_register" />
    <string name="UserName" />
</resources>